

Timi Turpeinen

ENGINEERING STUDENT

CONTACT



+358401964700



timi.turpeinen@gmail.com



Henttaan puistokatu 18

PROFILE

I'm a second-year student studying engineering physics and mathematics at Aalto-university. I have work experience from different fields and I'm used to working in teams. I'm efficient, diligent and always ready to learn new things quickly and efficiently.

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
 - o all programs
- R -programming
- Python
 - Machine Learning models
- Scala -programming
- C -programming
- Matlab
- Mathematica
- Problem solving
- Team working

LICENSES

- Occupational safety card, 2021
- Hygienepass, 2020
- Drivers license B 2020
- Drivers license AM 120, 2017

LANGUAGES

Mother tongue Finnish English Excellent

Swedish Fair

PROJECTS

Link to projects regarding of Computational Engineering and Mathematics and System Analysis

EDUCATION

Aalto-university

Engineering physics and mathematics 29.8.2022 -

- Major study: Mathematics and System Analysis
- · Minor study: Information Technology

Herttoniemen yhteiskoulun lukio

Matriculation examination graduate 2018 - 2021

Sipoon Lahdenkoulu

Primary school 2009 - 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Borealis Polymers Oy

In the duties of a loading operator in the material handling department.

Job description: Loading plastic pellets in to tankers and containers.

1.4.2021-30.6.2021

12.6.2023-25.8.2023

Sibbe Disc Golf (Alarauta Oy)

Disc golf course maintainer

- Job description:
 - o Selling tickets and disc golf products and maintaining a disc golf course
 - o Arranging disc golf tournaments NBDG
 - Tyyni 2019 & 2018
- 4.6.2018-30.6.2018
- 2.5.2019-31.8.2019

Sipoon kunta

Sipoo youth council

Youth councilor, municipal decisionmaking and representative's duties:

- Sipoon suomenkielinen koulutusjaosto
- Sosiaali- ja terveysvaliokunta

2016 - 2021

INTERESTS

Reading books, watching movies, gym, jogging, listening musics and learning new things.